Hudson River Sloop Clearwater, Inc. Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 1. Environmental Action, 1; 37.5 Linear Feet Boxes: 1 - 41 Folders: 1 - 1126
  - Subseries 1.8: Hazardous Waste, 1.8; Boxes: 7 - 8 Folders: 265 - 322
    - Lead Poisoning: Sources, Symptoms and Solutions (Folder 297, Box 7)
    - Monitoring of Past Radioactive Waste Ocean Dumpsites (Folder 298, Box 7)
    - NYS Hazardous Substances Bulk Storage Act May 1987 (Folder 299, Box 8)
    - NYS Hazardous Waste Facility Siting Plan October 1993 (Folder 300, Box 8)
    - NYS Hazardous Waste Manifest Guidance Manual (Folder 301, Box 8)
    - NYS Hazardous Waste Site Remedial Plan July 1990 (Folder 302, Box 8)
    - NYS Hazardous Waste Site Remedial Plan Aug 1989 (Folder 303, Box 8)
    - NYS Inactive Hazardous Waste Site Citizen Participation Plan (Folder 304, Box 8)
    - NYS Inactive Hazardous Waste Site Citizen Participation Plan: Responsiveness Summary (Folder 305, Box 8)
    - NYS Inactive Hazardous Waste Site Remedial Plan 1986 (Folder 306, Box 8)
    - NYS Inactive Hazardous Waste Site Remedial Plan Update and Status Report 1987 (Folder 307, Box 8)
    - Permitting Innovation: NY’s Hazardous Waste Research, Development and Demonstration Regulations (Folder 308, Box 8)
    - Pesticides (Folder 309, Box 8)
    - Poisoning the Public for Profit: Pesticide Use and Abuse in the Empire State (Folder 310, Box 8)
    - A Review of the Used Oil Management Program in NYS (Folder 311, Box 8)
    - Revised Draft: NYS Hazardous Waste Facility Siting Plan and Environmental Impact Statement Aug. 1989 (Folder 312, Box 8)
    - Risks for Congenital Malformations Associated with Residential Proximity to Hazardous Waste (Folder 313, Box 8)
    - Sanitary Landfills in NYS and the Potential for Hazardous Waste Dumping (Folder 314, Box 8)
    - Siting Board Jurisdiction: Hazardous Waste Side Remediation (Folder 315, Box 8)
    - Siting Manual for Storing Hazardous Substances (Folder 316, Box 8)
    - State Hazardous Waste Reduction Laws Comparison - New York, New Jersey, Massachusetts (Folder 317, Box 8)
    - State Hazardous Waste Reduction Laws - Massachusetts (Folder 318, Box 8)
    - State Hazardous Waste Reduction Laws - New Jersey (Folder 319, Box 8)
    - Storage of Hazardous Substances (Folder 320, Box 8)
    - The Voluntary Cleanup of New York’s Contaminated Property (Folder 321, Box 8)
    - Wastes in Marine Environments (Folder 322, Box 8)
  - Subseries 1.9: Hudson River Estuary Management (HREM), 1.9; Boxes: 8 - 9 Folders: 323 - 355
    Series contains documents and correspondence concerning fish management in the Hudson River
    - 1998 Year Class Report (Folder 323, Box 8)
    - Clippings (Folder 324, Box 8)
    - Comments on the NYS Draft HREM Plan (Folder 325, Box 8)
    - DEC 1976 Hudson River Fishery Resources (Folder 326, Box 8)
    - Draft HREM Plan for Internal Review (Folder 327, Box 8)
    - Estuarine Management Act (Folder 328, Box 8)
    - Hudson River Estuarine Sanctuary Reserves (Folder 329, Box 8)
    - HREM 1993 Annual Report (Folder 330, Box 8)
    - HREM Administrative Staff Minutes (Folder 331, Box 8)
    - HREM Advisory Committee (Folder 332, Box 9)
    - HREM Draft Plan (Folder 333, Box 9)
    - HREM Plan Testimony (Folder 334, Box 9)
    - HREM Program Funding (Folder 335, Box 9)
    - HREM Program Legal/Regulatory Issues (Folder 336, Box 9)
    - HREM Program: Strategy for the Development of a Fifteen Year (Folder 337, Box 9)
    - Hudson River Estuary Quarterly Issues Update and State of the Hudson Report: 1992 (Folder 338, Box 9)
    - Hudson River Estuary Quarterly Issues Update and State of the Hudson Report: 1993 (Folder 339, Box 9)
    - Hudson River Estuary Quarterly Issues Update and State of the Hudson Report: 1994 (Folder 340, Box 9)
    - Hudson River Estuary Quarterly Issues Update and State of the Hudson Report: 1995 (Folder 341, Box 9)
    - Hudson River Fisheries Unit (Folder 342, Box 9)
    - Hudson River National Estuarine Research Reserve: Draft Management Plan (Folder 343, Box 9)
    - Hudson River National Estuarine Research Reserve: Final Management Plan (Folder 344, Box 9)
    - Hudson River National Estuarine Research Reserve Update and Scientific Publications (Folder 345, Box 9)
    - Hudson River Regulatory Study (Folder 346, Box 9)
    - Legislative Add-ons and Additional Budget Matters (Folder 347, Box 9)
    - Limited Entry (Folder 348, Box 9)
    - Notes (legal size) (Folder 349, Box 9)
    - Public Hearing Comments on Draft HREM Plan (Folder 350, Box 9)
    - A Research Program for the Hudson River Estuary (Folder 351, Box 9)
    - A Research Program for the Hudson River Estuary: Report on the Development of an Estuarine Science Paradigm (Folder 352, Box 9)
    - Shad (Folder 353, Box 9)
    - Statement of Ivan P. Vamos: Hudson River Management Plan and Draft EIS (Folder 354, Box 9)
    - Sturgeon (Folder 355, Box 9)
  - Subseries 1.10: Wetlands/Transportation, 1.10; Boxes: 9 - 10 Folders: 356 - 389
    Series contains documents, research, and correspondence concerning transportation reconstruction on wetlands
    - City of Poughkeepsie Transportation Strategy (Folder 356, Box 9)
    - Port Authority Ferry Terminals (Folder 357, Box 9)
    - A Proposal to Enhance the Wetland Provisions of the Clean Water (Folder 358, Box 9)
    - Staten Island Naval Base Opposition (Folder 359, Box 9)
    - Transportation (Folder 360, Box 9)
    - Transportation Bill: Wetlands (Folder 361, Box 10)
    - Transportation: Infrastructure/ISTEA (Folder 362, Box 10)
    - Troy Barge Canal Terminal (Folder 363, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: Clippings (Folder 364, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: Comments on Proposed Revisions to the 1989 Federal Manual (Folder 365, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: Correspondence (Folder 366, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: Dutchess County Environmental Management Council Wetland Maps (Folder 367, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: Environmental Protection Agency Wetlands Action Plan Jan. ‘89 (Folder 368, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: Freshwater Wetlands Regulations (Folder 369, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: Freshwater Wetland Regulations Proposed Revisions 1990 (Folder 370, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: Freshwater Wetlands Report Aug. 1989 (Folder 371, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: Joint Wetlands Permits (Folder 372, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: Legislature (Folder 373, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: Meetings (Folder 374, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: National Audubon Society (Folder 375, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: National Research Council- “Restoration of Aquatic Ecosystems” (Folder 376, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: National Wetlands Priority Conservation Plan (Folder 377, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: New York State Tidal Wetlands Program (Folder 378, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: New York State Water Quality 1990 (Folder 379, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: New York State Water Quality 1992 (Folder 380, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: Notes (Folder 381, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: Pamphlets (Folder 382, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: Program Info Sheet (Folder 383, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: Public Awareness (Folder 384, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: Reports and Studies (Folder 385, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: River Project - Artificial Wetland (Folder 386, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: Route 32 Wetlands Restoration Project (Folder 387, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: Staten Island Freshwater Wetlands Program Environmental Impact Statement (Folder 388, Box 10)
    - Wetlands: The Corps of Engineers’ Administration of the Section 404 Program (Folder 389, Box 10)
  - Subseries 1.11: James Bay/Niagara, 1.11; Box: 11 Folders: 390 - 396
    Series contains documents concerning the power plant at James Bay/Niagara
    - James Bay (Folder Folder 390, Box 11)
    - James Bay II (Folder Folder 391, Box 11)
    - James Bay: Ben&Jerry’s (Folder Folder 392, Box 11)
    - James Bay Police Issue 1993 (Folder Folder 393, Box 11)
    - James Bay Project: A River Drowned by Water (Folder Folder 394, Box 11)
    - Niagara Mohawk Power Company (Folder Folder 395, Box 11)
    - Quebec Project (Folder Folder 396, Box 11)
  - Subseries 1.12: PCBs, 1.12; Boxes: 11 - 18 Folders: 397 - 563
    Series contains documents, studies, and correspondence concerning PCBs in the Hudson River and their effects on fish, other wildlife, and humans
    - 1990 Budget Issue (Folder 397, Box 11)
    - Action ‘96 (Folder 398, Box 11)
    - Action Alerts (Folder 399, Box 11)
    - Administrative Hearing 1982 (Folder 400, Box 11)
    - Administrative Hearing 1987-ALJ Rulings (Folder 401, Box 11)
    - Administrative Hearing 1987 Final Decision of Siting Board (Folder 402, Box 11)
    - Administrative Hearing 1987 General Electric Role (Folder 403, Box 11)
    - Administrative Hearing 1987-Party Motions, Discovery Requests (Folder 404, Box 11)
    - Amendment to Siting Law (Folder 405, Box 11)
    - Barge Canal Impacts (Folder 406, Box 11)
    - Biodegradation General Press (Folder 407, Box 11)
    - Biodegradation in Sediments (Folder 408, Box 11)
    - Biodegradation of PCBs in Hudson River Sediments, Feb. 1992 (Folder 409, Box 11)
    - Biodegradation of PCBs in Hudson River Sediments, Feb. 1992 (with notes) (Folder 410, Box 11)
    - Bioremediation of Sediments Conference (Folder 411, Box 11)
    - Clearwater Navigator on PCBs (Folder 412, Box 11)
    - Clearwater Response to PCB Treatment and Destruction (Folder 413, Box 11)
    - Clippings (Folder 414, Box 11)
    - Clippings (2) (Folder 415, Box 11)
    - Clippings (3) (Folder 416, Box 11)
    - Coalition Meetings Summer ‘94 (Folder 417, Box 11)
    - Contacts/Fax Transmissions (Folder 418, Box 11)
    - Contingent Valuation PCB Images (Folder 419, Box 12)
    - Contingent Valuation PCB Survey (Folder 420, Box 12)
    - Contingent Valuation PCB Survey Draft (Folder 421, Box 12)
    - Contingent Valuation PCB Survey Revised 3/17/97 (Folder 422, Box 12)
    - Contingent Valuation Theory (Folder 423, Box 12)
    - Correspondence (Folder 424, Box 12)
    - DEC Action Plan 1990 and EPA Decision (Folder 425, Box 12)
    - Draft Supplemental Environmental Impact Statement Notices (Folder 426, Box 12)
    - Dredging (Folder 427, Box 12)
    - East Hampton Baymen Association vs. General Electric (Folder 428, Box 12)
    - Effects of Coplanar PCB Contamination (Folder 429, Box 12)
    - Environmental Criteria and Assessment Office Non-cancer RfD Press (Folder 430, Box 12)
    - Environmental Impact Statement Hudson River PCB Reclamation Demonstration Project, Final Oct. 1982 (Folder 431, Box 12)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Assessment and Remediation of Contaminated Sediments (Folder 432, Box 12)
    - Environmental Protection Agency A.T.T.I.C. Program (Folder 433, Box 12)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Superfund Reassessment: Community Relations Plan (Folder 434, Box 12)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Superfund Reassessment: General (Folder 435, Box 12)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Superfund Reassessment: General Electric (Folder 436, Box 12)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Superfund Reassessment: Joint Liaison Group Meetings and Notes (Folder 437, Box 12)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Superfund Reassessment: Oversight Committee (Folder 438, Box 12)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Superfund Reassessment: Petitions to Re-open/Press (Folder 439, Box 12)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Superfund Reassessment: Public Hearings (Folder 440, Box 12)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Superfund Reassessment: Reconsideration of EPA ROD (Folder 441, Box 12)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Superfund Reassessment: Scientific and Technical Committee (Folder 442, Box 12)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Superfund Reassessment: Steering Committee (Folder 443, Box 12)
    - Environmental Protection Agency vs. Department of Transportation PCB Lawsuit (Folder 444, Box 12)
    - Federal Survey of PCBs in Atlantic Coast Bluefish (Folder 445, Box 12)
    - Fish/Anglers Surveys (Folder 446, Box 13)
    - Fishing Economic Impacts (Folder 447, Box 13)
    - Galson Remedial Corporation: Company History and Process Description (Folder 448, Box 13)
    - Gannet Newspapers (Folder 449, Box 13)
    - General Electric Bioreactor Experiment (Folder 450, Box 13)
    - General Electric Fort Edward Superfund Site (Folder 451, Box 13)
    - General Electric In-Situ Biodegradation Demonstration Project (Folder 452, Box 13)
    - Great Lakes (Folder 453, Box 13)
    - History of the PCB Project, John Saunders (Folder 454, Box 13)
    - Housatonic River, CT-MA (Folder 455, Box 13)
    - Hudson Falls 1993-1994 (Folder 456, Box 13)
    - Hudson Falls Clearwater Public Statements (Folder 457, Box 13)
    - Hudson Falls: Department of Environmental Conservation Information (Folder 458, Box 13)
    - Hudson Falls July 1993 Consent Order (Folder 459, Box 13)
    - Hudson Falls Monthly Progress Report February 1994 (Folder 460, Box 13)
    - Hudson Falls Monthly Progress Report March 1994 (Folder 461, Box 13)
    - Hudson Falls Monthly Progress Report April 1994 (Folder 462, Box 13)
    - Hudson Falls Monthly Progress Report May 1994 (Folder 463, Box 13)
    - Hudson Falls Monthly Progress Report July 1994 (Folder 464, Box 13)
    - Hudson Falls Phone and Meeting Notes (Folder 465, Box 13)
    - Hudson Falls Press Coverage (Folder 466, Box 13)
    - Hudson Falls Proposed Remedial Action Plan (Folder 467, Box 13)
    - Hudson Falls Quarterly Report (Folder 468, Box 13)
    - Hudson Falls: State Pollution Discharge Elimination System Permit (Folder 469, Box 13)
    - Hudson River Communities PCB Cleanup Petition (1) (Folder 470, Box 13)
    - Hudson River Communities PCB Cleanup Petition (2) (Folder 471, Box 13)
    - Hudson River Communities PCB Cleanup Petition (3) (Folder 472, Box 13)
    - Hudson River Environmental Society Conference (Folder 473, Box 13)
    - Hudson River Fish/Sediment PCB Analysis (Folder 474, Box 13)
    - Issue Review Materials (Folder 475, Box 13)
    - Issues Related to PCB Dredging in the Hudson River (Folder 476, Box 14)
    - The Last Rivermen (Folder 477, Box 14)
    - Managing PCBs in the Hudson/Raritan Estuary and the New York Bight Plan (Folder 478, Box 14)
    - Meeting 7/24/1992 Staff (Folder 479, Box 14)
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee (Folder 480, Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous Files (Folder 481, Box 14)
    - New Bedford Harbor (Folder 482, Box 14)
    - New Bedford Harbor Record of Decision Summary (Folder 483, Box 14)
    - NYS vs. EPA 1983 Lawsuit (Folder 484, Box 14)
    - PCB Fish Sampling Results (Folder 485, Box 14)
    - PCB Forums (Folder 486, Box 14)
    - PCB Health Study - Akwesasne (Folder 487, Box 14)
    - PCB in Striped Bass from New York Marine Waters (Folder 488, Box 14)
    - PCB Impact on Recreational Fishing General Articles (Folder 489, Box 14)
    - PCB Movement and Transformation in Acushnet Estuary Sediments (Folder 490, Box 14)
    - PCB Press Conference 7/25/89 (Folder 491, Box 14)
    - PCB Public Hearing Comments (Folder 492, Box 14)
    - PCB RAMP Scope of Work (Folder 493, Box 14)
    - PCB Reclamation Project: Deadline Extension (Folder 494, Box 14)
    - PCB Reclamation Project: DEC and Industrial Hazardous Waste Facility Siting Board Briefs (Folder 495, Box 14)
    - PCB Reclamation Project: DEC Progress Reports (Folder 496, Box 15)
    - PCB Reclamation Project: Final Decision (Folder 497, Box 15)
    - PCB Reclamation Project: General Electric (Folder 498, Box 15)
    - PCB Reclamation Project: Harza Engineering Company (Folder 499, Box 15)
    - PCB Reclamation Project: James M. Tiedje (Folder 500, Box 15)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Permit Application Information (Folder 501, Box 15)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Public Hearing Dec. 15, 1987 (Folder 502, Box 15)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript Feb. 25, 1987 (Folder 503, Box 15)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript Feb. 26, 1987 (Folder 504, Box 15)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript May 19, 1987 (Folder 505, Box 15)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript June 23, 1987 (Folder 506, Box 15)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript June 24, 1987 (Folder 507, Box 15)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript June 25, 1987 (Folder 508, Box 15)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript June 26, 1987 (Folder 509, Box 15)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript June 29, 1987 (Folder 510, Box 15)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript June 30, 1987 (Folder 511, Box 15)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript July 1, 1987 (Folder 512, Box 15)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript July 2, 1987 (Folder 513, Box 15)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing (Folder 514, Box 16)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript July 29, 1987 (Folder 515, Box 16)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript Aug. 17, 1987 (Folder 516, Box 16)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript Aug. 18, 1987 (Folder 517, Box 16)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript Aug. 19, 1987 (Folder 518, Box 16)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript Aug. 20, 1987 (Folder 519, Box 16)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript Aug. 24, 1987 (Folder 520, Box 16)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript Aug. 25, 1987 (Folder 521, Box 16)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript Aug. 26, 1987 (Folder 522, Box 16)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript Sep. 14, 1987 (Folder 523, Box 16)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript Sep. 15, 1987 (Folder 524, Box 16)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing (Folder 525, Box 17)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript Sep. 17, 1987 (Folder 526, Box 17)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript Sep. 21, 1987 (Folder 527, Box 17)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript Sep. 22, 1987 (Folder 528, Box 17)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript Oct. 7, 1987 (Folder 529, Box 17)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript Oct. 28, 1987 (Folder 530, Box 17)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript Oct. 29, 1987 (Folder 531, Box 17)
    - PCB Reclamation Project Siting Board Proceedings Hearing Transcript Nov. 17, 1987 (Folder 532, Box 17)
    - PCB Remnant Deposits (Folder 533, Box 17)
    - PCB Settlement Advisory Committee (Folder 534, Box 17)
    - PCBs and Attorney General Eliot Spitzer (Folder 535, Box 17)
    - PCBs and Cancer Risks (Folder 536, Box 17)
    - PCBs and Fish Results (Folder 537, Box 17)
    - PCBs at SUNY New Paltz, NY (Folder 538, Box 17)
    - PCBs in Resident Species 1991 Data (Folder 539, Box 17)
    - Pete Seeger correspondence and lyrics (Folder 540, Box 17)
    - Polychlorinated Biphenyl (Folder 541, Box 17)
    - Portland, Oregon (Folder 542, Box 17)
    - Pre-PCB Reclamation Project Information (Folder 543, Box 17)
    - Project Sponsor Group (1) (Folder 544, Box 17)
    - Project Sponsor Group (2) (Folder 545, Box 17)
    - Project Sponsor Group (3) (Folder 546, Box 18)
    - Project Sponsor Group (4) (Folder 547, Box 18)
    - RAMP Comments (Folder 548, Box 18)
    - Research and Development Program for the Destruction of PCBs (Folder 549, Box 18)
    - River Watch (Folder 550, Box 18)
    - Sediment Reports (Folder 551, Box 18)
    - Sheboygan River and Harbor (Folder 552, Box 18)
    - South Glens Falls Strip (Folder 553, Box 18)
    - Striped Bass and PCBs, 1989 (Folder 554, Box 18)
    - Studies and Reports (Folder 555, Box 18)
    - Summaries (Folder 556, Box 18)
    - Toxic Tour (Folder 557, Box 18)
    - Transactions of the Northeast Section of the Wildlife Society (Folder 558, Box 18)
    - Treat/Distreat: White Papers Project (Folder 559, Box 18)
    - Treatment Technologies for PCB Contaminated Sediment (Folder 560, Box 18)
    - United States Geological Survey Water Monitoring (Folder 561, Box 18)
    - Washington and Saratoga Company’s General Electric Remediation (Folder 562, Box 18)
    - Washington Lobbying Trip 4/29-4/30/91 (Folder 563, Box 18)
  - Subseries 1.13: Southside, 1.13; Boxes: 19 - 20 Folders: 564 - 641
    Series contains documents and plans for the reconstruction of New York's harbor
    By size, alphabetical
    - Appeal Brief Manuscript (Folder 564, Box 19)
    - Appeal Papers (Folder 565, Box 19)
    - Article 78 Procedure (Folder 566, Box 19)
    - Article 78 (stipulation) (Folder 567, Box 19)
    - Cases - Omits (Folder 568, Box 19)
    - Comments, Affidavits (Folder 569, Box 19)
    - “Experts” Statements Public Hearing (Folder 570, Box 19)
    - Federal Cases (NEPA) (Folder 571, Box 19)
    - Federal Landmark Status/Regs, etc. (Folder 572, Box 19)
    - HRSC Springside II (Folder 573, Box 19)
    - Memo of Law (Folder 574, Box 19)
    - Notes (Folder 575, Box 19)
    - Petition Exhibits (Folder 576, Box 19)
    - Poughkeepsie Charter/Ordinance (Folder 577, Box 19)
    - Issues - Procedural (Folder 578, Box 19)
    - SEQR Regs (Folder 579, Box 19)
    - State Cases (Folder 580, Box 19)
    - State Historic Preservation Act (Folder 581, Box 19)
    - Stipulation Documents, etc. (Folder 582, Box 19)
    - Stipulation Miscellaneous (Folder 583, Box 19)
    - Stover Affidavit (Folder 584, Box 19)
    - Zoning and Planning (Folder 585, Box 19)
    - Affidavit of Service (Folder 586, Box 20)
    - Agreement (Folder 587, Box 20)
    - Agreement Draft (Folder 588, Box 20)
    - Affidavits in Support of Petition (Folder 589, Box 20)
    - Alderborgh Affidavit (Folder 590, Box 20)
    - Alderborgh Record of the Proceedings (Folder 591, Box 20)
    - Andrew Jackson Downing (Folder 592, Box 20)
    - Appeal Covers (Folder 593, Box 20)
    - Appendix (Folder 594, Box 20)
    - Application for Zoning Permit (Folder 595, Box 20)
    - Background Documents (Folder 596, Box 20)
    - Bersak Affidavit (Folder 597, Box 20)
    - Brief for Petitioners - Applicants (Folder 598, Box 20)
    - Common Council 2/6/1984 (Folder 599, Box 20)
    - Common Council Minutes (Folder 600, Box 20)
    - Conflict of Interest (Folder 601, Box 20)
    - Conditions of Approval (Folder 602, Box 20)
    - Contacts (Folder 603, Box 20)
    - Correspondence (Folder 604, Box 20)
    - EAF Application (Folder 605, Box 20)
    - Evaluation Report RE: Restoration and Development (Folder 606, Box 20)
    - Exhibits (Folder 607, Box 20)
    - Friends of the Shawangunks (Folder 608, Box 20)
    - Historical Landscape Report (Folder 609, Box 20)
    - Landmarks (Folder 610, Box 20)
    - Minutes 10/15/1982 (Folder 611, Box 20)
    - Minutes 11/15/1982 (Folder 612, Box 20)
    - Minutes 9/27/1083 (Folder 613, Box 20)
    - Minutes 10/11/1983 (Folder 614, Box 20)
    - Minutes 10/25/1983 (Folder 615, Box 20)
    - Minutes 11/22/1983 (Folder 616, Box 20)
    - Minutes 12/6/1983 (Folder 617, Box 20)
    - Minutes 11/22/1984 (Folder 618, Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous Files (Folder 619, Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous Papers (Folder 620, Box 20)
    - Miscellany (Folder 621, Box 20)
    - Notice of Issue (Folder 622, Box 20)
    - Notice of Petition (Folder 623, Box 20)
    - Offers of Help (Folder 624, Box 20)
    - Papers/HOC, etc. (Folder 625, Box 20)
    - Petition (Folder 626, Box 20)
    - Petition Pre-facts (Folder 627, Box 20)